<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="77">
    <version>1.2.0.0</version>
	<author>Courseplay.devTeam, tn4799</author>
	<title>
		<en>Challenge Mode</en>
		<de>Wettkampfmodus</de>
		<fr>Challenge Mode</fr>
	</title>

	<description>
        <en><![CDATA[
Challenge Time!
This mod provides everything you need to create your own challenge.
Custom Ingame UI with extra password to configure the rule set and values to your needs.
The password can only be changed by the server admin.

The following Values can be set to get a point:
- How much Money (without credits).
- How many Liters of each fruit.
- The amount of area you own (HA).
- Animals when grown up.

Additional Rules:
- How many points are needed to win
- A storage limit. Anything above that value won't be count.
- Helper limit 0-6.
- Animal Husbandry 0-6.
- Rent Vehicles for mission and shop/ only in the shop, or turn it off completly.
- Turn off specific mission types.
- Set a mission limit per farm from 0-8 missions active at the same time.
- Loan on/off/limited to a specified value.
- Mark vehicles and tools as starter to not count them into the points.
- Add or reduce points of a farm with a reason (e.g. won a challenge, punishment) with a complete log! The reason can be displayed by double clicking the entry.
- Hide a farm that doesn't participate in the challenge (e.g. Contractor). That farm will get have the limits set to max, is allowed to hire helpers and rent vehicles.

What is planed for the future:
- Integration of the Limited Daily Income Mod into the rule set to configure those limits within the same UI

We suggest you for a 24/7 Server to use the Mod limited daily income, for more fairness.

For more information, help, and report issues please visit <a href="https://github.com/Courseplay/ChallengeMode_FS22">github</a>.

Changelog
V1.0.0.1
 - fixed farm visiblity bug

V1.1.0.0
 - added an option to set an amount of ingame months for how long the challange lasts. Once the end of the last month is reached no more new points will be counted. If you set the Months to 0 you turn off this feature

V1.1.0.1
 - fixed mp synchronization of start vehicles

V1.2.0.0
 - Added an option for decreasing points if farm has a loan
 - Added an option to hide the other farms points, or pay to spy on the points as long as you are inside the menu
]]>
</en>
		<de><![CDATA[
Zeit für einen Wettkampf!
Diese Mod bietet euch alles um euren eigenen Wettkampf auszutragen.
Ein eigenes Menü mit einem eigenen Passwort um die Regeln und Werte auf die eigenen Bedürfnisse anzupassen.
Das Passwort kann nur durch einen Serveradministator geändert werden.

Diese Punkte können angepasst werden um Punkte zu bekommen:
- Geld auf dem Konto (ohne Kredit)
- Wie viel Liter pro Frucht (in eurem Besitz).
- Die gesamte Fläche, die ihr besitzt (HA)
- Ausgewachsene Tiere

Weitere Regeln:
- Wie viele Punkte zum Sieg nötig sind.
- Ein Limit wie viel Frucht gezählt werden soll (alles was darüber hinaus ist, wird nicht gezählt).
- Helferlimit 0-6.
- Tierstalllimit pro Farm 0-6.
- Fahrzeuge mieten für Missionen und im Shop / nur im Shop, oder komplett deaktiviert.
- Bestimmte Missionstypen deaktivieren.
- Ein Missionslimit pro Farm von 0-8 aktiven Missionen zur selben Zeit.
- Kredit an/aus/limitiert auf einen bestimmten Wert.
- Fahrzeuge und Geräte als Startfuhrpark markieren, so dass diese nicht zu den Punkten zählen.
- Punkte zu einer Farm hinzufügen oder abziehen (z.B. eine Challenge gewonnen oder eine Bestrafung), mit komplettem Verlauf! Der Grund kann mit einem Doppelklick auf den Eintrag angezeigt werden.
- Verstecke eine Farm, die nicht an dem Wettkampf teilnimmt (z.B. Lohnunternehmen). Diese Farm hat die Limits aufs Maximum gesetzt und darf Helfer einstellen, sowie Fahrzeuge mieten.

Was ist für die Zukunft geplant:
- Die Einstellungsoptionen der Limits des Mod Tägliche Einkommensbegrenzung in das UI integrieren.

Wir empfehlen euch für einen 24/7 Server für mehr Fairness die Mod Tägliche Einkommensbegrenzung zu nutzen.

Für mehr Informationen, Hilfe und Fehlermeldungen, schaut bitte auf <a href="https://github.com/Courseplay/ChallengeMode_FS22">Github</a> vorbei.

Änderungsverlauf
V1.0.0.1
 - Fehler mit der Sichtbarkeit von Farmen behoben

V1.1.0.0
 - Es kann nun eine Dauer des Wettkampfes in Spiel-Monaten angegeben werden. Wurde das Ende des letzten Monats erreicht, werden keine neuen Punkte mehr gezählt. Wenn man die Dauer auf 0 Monate setzt dann ist das Feature deaktiviert.

V1.1.0.1
 - Fehler mit der Synchronisierung der Startfahrzeuge behoben

V1.2.0.0
 - Option hinzugefügt, dass ein Hof Punkte verliert, sollte der Hof einen Kredit haben
 - Option hinzugefügt um die Punktezusammensetzung der anderen Farmen zu verstecken, oder bazahle um die Punkte zu sehen solange du im Menü bist
]]></de>
       <fr><![CDATA[
Voici le Farming compétitif !
Ce mod vous permet de définir un ensemble de règles pour vous fixer un défi en solo ou en multi.
Configurer les paramètres du challenge via le nouvel onglet dans le menu du jeu.
Le mot de passe ne peut être changé que par l'administrateur du serveur.

Les données suivantes peuvent servir à attribuer des points :
- Combien d'agent sur le compte (déduction faite des emprunts).
- Combien de litres de chaque culture.
- Combien de surface possédée (Ha).
- Combien d'animaux adultes.

Règles supplémentaires:
- Combien de points sont nécessaire pour gagner
- Stockage maximum. Tout excédent ne sera pas comptabilisé.
- Limite d'ouvriers 0-6.
- Limite de stabulations 0-6.
- Location de véhicules pour les contrats, depuis le magasin ou complètement interdite.
- Suppression de certains types de contrats.
- Limite de contrats actifs en même temps par ferme de 0 à 8.
- Emprunt autorisé/interdit/jusqu'à un montant défini.
- Désignation des véhicules et outils de démarrage comme exclus du comptage de points.
- Ajout ou soustraction de points à une ferme possible avec justification (exemple : pénalité, bon esprit, bonification) avec suivi des actions ! La justification apparait en double cliquant sur l'entrée du journal.
- Masquage d'une ferme ne participant pas au challenge (exemple une ETA ou une ferme Admin). Cette ferme n'aura pas de limites, pour utiliser des ouvriers et louer des véhicules.

Dans les évolutions futures:
- Integration du mod de limitation des revenus journaliers au sein des règles dans la même interface.

Nous vous suggérons d'utiliser un serveur dédié 24/24 7/7 si vous utilisez la limitation des revenus journaliers pour plus d'équité.

Pour plus d'imformations, demande de support ou déclaration de bugs, rendez-vous sur le <a href="https://github.com/Courseplay/ChallengeMode_FS22">github</a>.

Changelog
V1.0.0.1
 - correction du bug de visibilité des fermes

V1.1.0.0
 - ajout d'une option pour définir la durée du challenge exprimée en mois. Une fois la fin du dernier mois du challenge atteinte, les points ne seront plus comptés. Cette fonction peut être désactivée en mettant la valeur à 0

V1.1.0.1
 - correction de la synchronisation des véhicules de démarrage
]]>
</fr>
    </description>

	<iconFilename>Icon_ChallengeMode.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/Util.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/main.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/VictoryPointsUtil.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="gui/ScoreBoardFrame.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="gui/dialogs/AddPointsDialog.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/ScoreBoardElement.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/ScoreBoardCategory.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/ScoreBoardList.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/VictoryPoint.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/VictoryPointManager.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/Rules.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/RuleManger.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/ChangeElementEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/JoinEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/ChangeAdminPasswordEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/ChangeFarmVisibilityEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/ChangeGoalEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/ChangeDurationEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/ChallengeOverEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/AddPointsEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/ChangeIsStartVehicleEvent.lua"/>
		<sourceFile filename="events/PayToSpyEvent.lua"/>
	</extraSourceFiles>

	<l10n filenamePrefix="translations/translation" />
</modDesc>
